Thank you for watching!
Hello everyone! This is Kumamon!
Do you know where we are?
We are here in front of Yachiyo Station, Yachiyo City, Kumamoto Prefecture!
And I'm Mirei Hoshino, lucky number 7 in Eibei Fine Arts Private School.
Once again, I am here in Yachiyo City, Kumamoto Prefecture!
I have been to Kumamoto Prefecture before. I have memories of eating a lot of sashimi.
I have never been to Yachiyo City. This is my first time here. This is my first time in Yachiyo City.
The image of Kumamoto Prefecture is that Kumamoto Dai-senpai and...Tatami is Kumamoto? Right?
Tatami is the image of Kumamoto. What Kumamoto is holding in its hand... this?
What? Egg yolk?
Banpaille? Vinpaille?
What? This? It's huge!
That's huge! I wonder what it tastes like!
Speaking of Hoshina's favorite food...
My favorite food is strawberries!
Do you know why I was invited to Yatsuchira's journal today?
What? What is it? I was told suddenly that I'm going to Kumamoto.
What is it already? I'm here all over the place.
Strawberry farm
So here we are at the strawberry farm!
Thank you very much!
There are so many strawberries!
The moment I entered the farm, I could smell the sweet aroma of strawberries.
I was so excited!
Now, I would like to talk to Mr. Kuroda, the owner of this strawberry farm.
Mr. Kuroda from this strawberry farm!
Please let's talk to Mr. Kuroda!
Please take care of them!
There are a lot of strawberries like this.
Why are strawberries so popular here in Yatsushiro?
The temperature is relatively warm in Yatsukeshiro.
It's a good environment for growing strawberries.
I think it's because it's a good environment for growing strawberries.
Also, the water is clean.
The water is rich in millenals and other elements.
which makes strawberries tasty.
It's a perfect environment for strawberry lovers.
I love them so much!
I can't stop being excited!
Thank you very much!
The variety Eubenity is a Kumamoto variety.
I named my strawberries
It's called "Ebi Berry".
Shrimp Berry!
I'm naming them "Shrimp Berry".
This is so shrimpy!
I know, right?
Amazing!
I feel a connection!
Why shrimpberry?
I have two theories.
The manager of the café I'm going to right now
When the manager of the café where I'm going to pick up the strawberries
He said, "We call them prawns.
Strawberries?
Yes, sir.
He said we call our strawberries "prawns" because they look like prawns.
So we call them prawns.
I thought it was funny.
So I decided to call them prawns.
And one more...
We use the water from the river
So we use the water from the river.
and the other is that the water is drawn from the river, so it's like a shrimp that grows in the river.
There are two theories.
Wow!
No way!
That's right! Because of the shrimp connection
I want to eat a lot of shrimpberries!
You know how to get them, right?
Those strawberries.
From here.
With a snap of the wrist
Snap! With a snap of the wrist.
Can I try?
Snap!
Yeah, yeah! That's good!
It's good! Yes!
Bon appétit!
It's so good!
Thank you!
I think they are ripe and delicious!
The flavor is so strong! Amazing!
Too delicious!
I recommend eating strawberries in the shade.
Why is that?
Well, they grow in the shade, so they're cooler.
Right now they're a little hot.
You're right.
They're hiding these things.
Like this one.
I think it's delicious.
It's definitely a little cooler and tastier than the one you just had.
It's true.
There are many places where strawberries are grown in the backcountry.
But I use the soil here.
It's like the whole soil is nourished with nutrients.
It's packed with sweetness, but it's also quite refreshing.
Yes, the Ubini variety has a good balance of acidity and sweetness.
It's extremely delicious.
Thank you very much.
Please eat as much as you can.
I'll eat a lot.
I can't stop.
It's so good! Oh my God, it's so big!
It's heavy and quite sturdy.
Delicious!
I'm always called "Fruit Monster".
Oh, I see.
I eat almost all the fruit that is brought to my dressing room.
Well, I'd like to pick some strawberries for cooking later.
I want to put them in here.
I'm going to eat them.
It's something, isn't it, like, the more the heel is facing up, the more vigorous it is?
Yes, delicious
I've heard that such a thing is more delicious
Wow! I found strawberries in the shade!
Let's eat them!
Eat up...
Let's have some!
Delicious!
This one is cold too.
This is cold, too.
I want some!
This big one.
I found it.
This one is probably very cold.
Hikari Ichigo
They are absolutely delicious!
The leaves...
Mm-hm-hm!
Wow! Delicious!
It's cool!
It's delicious!
It's totally different!
Hurry up and harvest! He said.
They're eating so much!
Please take more and more!
He's eating so much! I'm sorry!
We've got a pretty good harvest.
I'm trying to pick different kinds of strawberries.
Some are small, some are big, but they are all very red and beautiful!
Strawberries in the shade
We harvested a lot!We harvested so many!
They all look so delicious!
I will be cooking with them later!
Enjoy!
Cat Hunt to Hoshinanire!
Let's go!
Are there 10 cats?
Are there really 10 cats?
Isn't it pretty close to there?
Let's take a picture of this view!
I really don't see them.
Cats?
Is there a cat? I don't think so.
There's a cat.
There was a dog.
I heard a dog.
I don't know if it's too loud.
What?
Is it hay fever? Your nose is runny. My cat has hay fever, too.
You got company? Where are you? Tell me.
Do you know where the other kids are? You know where they are? You tell me. I'm sleepy.
I'll see you later.
It's nice of you to let me know you're not here.
I don't see him. He's coming.
I'll be right back.
It's like this.
I can count on you.
I'm counting on you.
I couldn't find any cats... so I'm going to try again. I'll try to find a cat tentatively.
I wonder if I'll be able to meet him, because he's only one cat.
I'm the only one.
I'll see if I can find one. I got it! Yes!
I got it!
It wasn't the cute mother sound, it was her running away.
I saw it... the third one.
Wow!
See you in the next video!
Bye-bye!
They're looking at each other.
They're so cute.
One, two, three, four, five, six?
I don't think there are 4 more.
Goal!
So we ended up with 6 cats.
The cats made me feel so relaxed.
And the weather was nice and sunny.
I think it was a great walk!
I've never done this before, and it's a rare experience.
Oh!
Oh, it's delicious!
It's finished!